

PROFILE

Information Technology graduate friendly and dedicated, passionate in terms of Programming. Highly capable leader, having led multiple class projects and capstone to completion. Excited to leverage skills gained from school, researches and On the Job Training (OJT) to become an IT worker. Willing to work on your company with your terms and condition.

CONTACT

PHONE: +639614358034

EMAIL:

karlen.legaspi20@gmail.com

Facebook:

<u>Karlen Marx Engello Legaspi |</u> <u>Facebook</u>

SKILLS

Javascript	30%
PHP	40%
Android Dev	60%
JAVA	50%
MS PowerPoint	60%
MS Word	60%
MS PowerPoint	60%

KARLEN MARX ENGELLO A. LEGASPI

EDUCATION

Samar State University

June 2015 – May 2018 Competency Based on Vocational Education Major in Electrical Technology

Samar State University

August 2018 – July 2022 Bachelor of Science in Information Technology Capstone Project and Research

WORK EXPERIENCE

January 2022 - July 2022

- > On the Job Training
- Samar State University
- Capstone Project Leader
- Online Public Market Vendor of the City of Catbalogan
 - Design and layout mobile application
 - Programmer
 - Coding
 - Accomplished Capstone Paper-works

July 2022 - April 2023

- > Freelancer
 - Android Development/JAVA LANGUAGE
 - 1. Passenger Information Coder with QR code
 - 2. Sign Language Detector App
 - 3. INGCO ECOMERCE APP
 - 4. Real-time Emergency Reporting System based in Barangay 09 of Catbalogan City
 - Snow Cabbage Detection and Recommendation using CNN
 - 6. Pest Detector Application
 - 7. KOMI: An art Commission and Sharing Mobile App

PERSONAL REFERENCES

Angeline A. Rafales

Email: rafalesabelidoangeline02@gmail.com

Phone number: +639700556813